WILLIAM MYERS

5418 Monroe Avenue, Evansville, IN 47715 | C: 812-582-9264 | william.cherokee.myers@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a dedicated and hardworking Web Developer who is experienced with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap. I have a history working with WordPress, HubSpot CMS, and EVOQ CMS. I have a basic understanding of PHP, MySql, and the Adobe Suite.

SKILLS

- Oral and written communications
- Strong analytical skills
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Works well in a team environment and independently
- Deep understanding of HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Experience with JIRA, Bynder, WordPress and Adobe Suite
- Basic understanding of PHP, SQL, Java and COBOL

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

May 2024

Bachelor of Science: Geology, Minor – Geography **University of Southern Indiana** — Evansville, IN

May 2020

Associate of Applied Science: Computer and Information Technology **Henderson Community College** — Henderson, KY

WORK HISTORY

08/2020 to Present Web Developer SS&C Technologies – Evansville, IN

09/2019 to 05/2020 Software Developer OneMain Financial – Evansville, IN

08/2018 to 09/2019 Intern – Software Development OneMain Financial – Evansville, IN